projectorpsa.com 2016-04-22

# Professional Services Automation from Projector PSA - Privacy Policy

## Introduction

We at Projector PSA, Inc. are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information that you share with us. This document (the “Privacy Policy”) describes the online privacy practices for this web site (the “Site”) and discloses the types of information that we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it. For information on Projector PSA's commitment to handling personal information in accordance with the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles published by the U.S. Department of Commerce please click here.

## Changes to the Privacy Policy

All information that can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains (“Personal Information”) that we collect through the Site is subject to the version of the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of such collection. Projector PSA reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy without prior notice.

## Collection of Personal Information

You may access the majority of the information on the Site without providing any Personal Information to Projector PSA. However, certain activities such as downloading software or accessing the support area, may require that you provide certain information about yourself via an online form or e-mail. You may choose whether or not to provide this information to Projector PSA. Opting out of providing Personal Information may mean that you will be unable to access certain parts of the Site.

## How Personal Information is Used

Projector PSA may collect Personal Information through email, chat or online forms to support your use or potential use of the products and services provided by Projector PSA. Information collected by Projector PSA will not be shared with any other companies or organizations unless legally required to do so, or if we believe that your actions violate applicable laws or the Site’s Terms of Use.

Projector PSA may share Personal Information with our affiliates and contractors to allow them to perform functions on our behalf. In such event that Personal Information is shared with affiliates and contractors, it will only be shared to the extent reasonably necessary for them to perform their functions and they will not be authorized to use it for any other function.

Projector PSA will not communicate any information to you regarding products, services, and special offers available from Projector PSA without your consent.

## How Non-Personal Information is Used

Projector PSA may automatically collect information about the use of the Site, such as the types of services used and how many users we receive daily. This information is collected in aggregate form, without identifying any user individually. Projector PSA may use this aggregate, non-identifying statistical data for statistical analysis, marketing or similar promotional purposes.

## Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

The Site may utilize “cookies” or other tracking technologies. A cookie is a small text file that can store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to the Site and can only be read by the web Site that gave it to you. Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names, Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser and operating system versions, and dates and times the Site was accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to understand how our Site and services are being used and to improve your experience on the Site.

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it, or to prevent the use of cookies altogether. Some of the web pages on the Site require the use of cookies, so users choosing not to accept cookies may not be able to access those pages.

## Changing Personal Information

You have the right to access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences at any time by utilizing the appropriate page on the Site or by e-mailing us at [privacy@projectorpsa.com](mailto:privacy@projectorpsa.com). We will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in your Personal Information.

## Privacy of Children

The Site is not intended to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age.

## Your Consent

By using this web Site, you consent to the terms of our Privacy Policy as stated above. Should this Privacy Policy change, you will be deemed to have been made aware of, and will be subject to, the changes to the Privacy Policy by your continued use of the Site.
